<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- General Settings-->
  <IH_GeneralSettings>General Settings</IH_GeneralSettings>
  
  <IH_tickRateSingle>Immortal tick rate(1x speed)</IH_tickRateSingle>
  <IH_tickRateSingleTip>A seperate tick rate for when the game is running at 1x speed or auto slowdown mode. This allows much more frequent ticks without so much worry about performance</IH_tickRateSingleTip>
  <IH_tickRate>Immortal tick rate</IH_tickRate>
  <IH_tickRateTip>How often all immotals heal in game ticks. Default speed is 60 ticks per second so at the default of 250 an immortal would heal every 4ish seconds. Healing speeds are multiplied by the ticks passed so there should be no change to healing rate.</IH_tickRateTip>
  <IH_tickRateRare>Multiplier for rare ticks</IH_tickRateRare>
  <IH_tickRateRareTip>Roughly how many immortal ticks happen before a pawn will do things like attempt to regrow a limb or heal a scar.(Only uses base immortal tick rate, not 1x)</IH_tickRateRareTip>

  <IH_disableFlashstorm>Safe flashstorms</IH_disableFlashstorm>
  <IH_disableFlashstormTip>Makes flashstorms that spawn from a beheaded immortal not start fires or do damage.</IH_disableFlashstormTip>
 
  <IH_firstDeathGrantsQuickening>Unknown Immortal Quickening</IH_firstDeathGrantsQuickening>
  <IH_firstDeathGrantsQuickeningTip>Enables/Disables if you can gain immortality from a pawn who hasent had their first death.</IH_firstDeathGrantsQuickeningTip>

  <IH_ShowImmortalNumbers>Reveal Immortality numbers</IH_ShowImmortalNumbers>
  <IH_ShowImmortalNumbersTip>Reveals the specific healing factor for immortal pawns</IH_ShowImmortalNumbersTip>

  <!-- General Immortality Settings-->
  <IH_GeneralImmortalitySettings>General Immortality Settings</IH_GeneralImmortalitySettings>
  
  <IH_DeathEffectOnVal>Effect of deaths On immortality,</IH_DeathEffectOnVal>
  <IH_DeathEffectOnValTip>A pawns immortality value will change by this number whenever they die.</IH_DeathEffectOnValTip>

  <IH_baseHealSpeed>Healing Rate relative to 1: </IH_baseHealSpeed>
  <IH_baseHealSpeedTip>Adjusts how fast a pawn will heal wounds and come back to life.</IH_baseHealSpeedTip>

  <IH_scarHealSpeed>Scar heal speed</IH_scarHealSpeed>
  <IH_scarHealSpeedTip>A multiplier for how fast scars heal. scars are only healed in rare ticks and at a much slower rate. At 1 a scar will heal about 1 severity per quadrum.</IH_scarHealSpeedTip>


  <IH_immortalTransferBodyFactor>Body size quickening factor</IH_immortalTransferBodyFactor>
  <IH_immortalTransferBodyFactorTip>Determines how much the body size of a creature impacts the amount of immortality gained. 0 means no impact. 1 means 100%. The calculation is exponential so at 200% a creature with a body size of 2 will grant 4 times the immortality.</IH_immortalTransferBodyFactorTip>
  <IH_immortalHealingBodyFactor>Body size heal factor </IH_immortalHealingBodyFactor>
  <IH_immortalHealingBodyFactorTip>Determines how much the body size of a creature impacts the rate at which they heal. 0 mean no impact. 1 means 100% so a creature with a body size of 2 would heal twice as fast. At 200% the same creature would heal 4 times as fast</IH_immortalHealingBodyFactorTip>


  <!-- Regrowth Settigns-->
  <IH_regrowth>Regrowth Settings</IH_regrowth>
  
  <IH_regrowSpeed>Regrowth Speed: </IH_regrowSpeed>
  <IH_regrowSpeedTip>The Speed at which a pawn will regrow limbs and organs</IH_regrowSpeedTip>
  <IH_regrowMaxParts>Max parts regrowing</IH_regrowMaxParts>
  <IH_regrowMaxPartsTip>Limits the number of activly regrowing parts to this number. Does not affect vital organs that start regrowing while a pawn is dead.</IH_regrowMaxPartsTip>
  <IH_regrowCostsNoFood>Enable regrowth food cost </IH_regrowCostsNoFood>
  <IH_regrowCostsNoFoodTip>Enables/Disables the acceleration of a pawns hunger while they are regenerating limbs and organs</IH_regrowCostsNoFoodTip>
  <IH_regrowCostsFood>Regrowth Food Cost: </IH_regrowCostsFood>
  <IH_regrowCostsFoodTip>The food cost of regrowth is multiplied by this value</IH_regrowCostsFoodTip>

  <IH_accumulateFoodNeed>Hunger accumuation multiplier</IH_accumulateFoodNeed>
  <IH_accumulateFoodNeedTip>While pawns are regenerating and starving or dead they will gain a hediff that increases hunger. Spending time not starving reduces this.</IH_accumulateFoodNeedTip>

  <IH_perStageHp>Part Regrowth Hp</IH_perStageHp>
  <IH_perStageHpTip>Adjusts the values of max part Hp per immortality stage, these values are added to the severity multiplier</IH_perStageHpTip>
  
  <IH_regrowLesser>Lesser Immortal</IH_regrowLesser>
  <IH_regrowLesserTip>Max base HP of a part a lesser immortal can regrow.</IH_regrowLesserTip>
  <IH_regrowImmortal>Immortal</IH_regrowImmortal>
  <IH_regrowImmortalTip>Max base HP of a part an immortal can regrow.</IH_regrowImmortalTip>
  <IH_regrowGreater>Greater Immortal</IH_regrowGreater>
  <IH_regrowGreaterTip>Max base HP of a part a greater immortal can regrow.</IH_regrowGreaterTip>
  <IH_regrowHigh>High Immortal</IH_regrowHigh>
  <IH_regrowHighTip>Max base HP of a part a high immortal can regrow.</IH_regrowHighTip>
  <IH_regrowGrand>Grand Immortal</IH_regrowGrand>
  <IH_regrowGrandTip>Max base HP of a part a grand immortal can regrow.</IH_regrowGrandTip>
  <IH_regrowApex>Apex Immortal</IH_regrowApex>
  <IH_regrowApexTip>Max base HP of a part an apex immortal can regrow.</IH_regrowApexTip>
  
  <!-- Default and Utility Stuff-->
  <IH_defaultAll>Default settings</IH_defaultAll>
  <IH_defaultAllTip>Shows several check boxes to select what sections to default</IH_defaultAllTip>


  <IH_defaultImmortalClasses>Immortal classes</IH_defaultImmortalClasses>
  <IH_defaultImmortalClassesTip>Removes all immortal classes and regenerates them using default values</IH_defaultImmortalClassesTip>
  <IH_defaultDefaultImmortal>Default immortality</IH_defaultDefaultImmortal>
  <IH_defaultDefaultImmortalTip>Reset the default immortality settings. As in the settings for things without an immortality class or any setting in an immortality class that uses default</IH_defaultDefaultImmortalTip>
  <IH_defaultRegrowth>Regrowth</IH_defaultRegrowth>
  <IH_defaultRegrowthTip>Reset the per stage regrowth settings to default values.</IH_defaultRegrowthTip>
  <IH_defaultGeneralImmortal>General immortality</IH_defaultGeneralImmortal>
  <IH_defaultGeneralImmortalTip>Reset things like healing/regrowth rates</IH_defaultGeneralImmortalTip>
  <IH_defaultGeneral>General</IH_defaultGeneral>
  <IH_defaultGeneralTip>Reset general settings like tick rate and immortality numbers</IH_defaultGeneralTip>
  <IH_defaultQuickeningChange>Quickening pawn chances</IH_defaultQuickeningChange>
  <IH_defaultQuickeningChangeTip>Resets the settings that govern how a pawn changes when they get a quickening.</IH_defaultQuickeningChangeTip>
  <IH_defaultTransfer>Transfer</IH_defaultTransfer>
  <IH_defaultTransferTip>Resets the settings that govern pawns gaining immortality from eating severed heads and stunted immortals</IH_defaultTransferTip>
  <IH_defaultHediffs>Custom Hediffs</IH_defaultHediffs>
  <IH_defaultHediffsTip>Resets all the changed hediffs.</IH_defaultHediffsTip>
  
  <IH_removeImmortality>Remove Immortality</IH_removeImmortality>
  <IH_removeImmortalityTip>Removes ALL immortality from EVERY pawn in the game, this cannot be reversed</IH_removeImmortalityTip>
  <IH_addImmortality>Add Immortality</IH_addImmortality>
  <IH_addImmortalityTip>Attempts to add immortality to every pawn both on the current map and in the world</IH_addImmortalityTip>

  <IH_defaultConfirm>Confirm?</IH_defaultConfirm>

  
  <!-- Default Immortality-->
  <IH_defaultImmortality>Default Immortality Settings</IH_defaultImmortality>
  
  <IH_chance>hidden immortality: </IH_chance>
  <IH_chanceTip>Hidden immortality or pre first death, in this state the pawn has no benefits of their immortality until they die.</IH_chanceTip>
  <IH_chanceVisible>visible immortality: </IH_chanceVisible>
  <IH_chanceVisibleTip>Visible immortality or post first death, an immortal in this state has full benefits from their immortality. This is the chance a hidden immortal will have their immortality increased to a value between the range below. </IH_chanceVisibleTip>

  <IH_ImmortalClassRange>Immortality range: </IH_ImmortalClassRange>
  <IH_ImmortalClassRangeTip>The minimum and maximum levels of immortality that a visible immortal will spawn with</IH_ImmortalClassRangeTip>
  <IH_ImmortalClassTransferIn>Immortality in: </IH_ImmortalClassTransferIn>
  <IH_ImmortalClassTransferInTip>An extra multiplier for a pawn who is gaining immortality power from another. All incoming immortality from quickenings is multiplied by this number.</IH_ImmortalClassTransferInTip>
  <IH_ImmortalClassTransferOut>Immortal out: </IH_ImmortalClassTransferOut>
  <IH_ImmortalClassTransferOutTip>An extra multiplier for a pawn who is giving immortality power to another. All outgoing immortality from quickenings is multiplied by this number.</IH_ImmortalClassTransferOutTip>
  
  
  <!-- Quickening Change Stuff-->
  <IH_quickeningChange>Quickening pawn changes</IH_quickeningChange>

  <IH_learningMult>Skill experience transfer</IH_learningMult>
  <IH_learningMultTip>Skill experience is multiplied by this after it is calculated what to give to the reciever of a quickening</IH_learningMultTip>
  <IH_passionChance>Passion gain chance</IH_passionChance>
  <IH_passionChanceTip>The chance that a pawn will recieve a passion from a pawn during quickening. Each chance can increase a passion from none to minor or from minor to major.</IH_passionChanceTip>
  <IH_passionChances>Passion gain chances</IH_passionChances>
  <IH_passionChancesTip>The number of times per quickening that a chance is rolled to gain a passion or increase a passion</IH_passionChancesTip>
  <IH_passionLoss>Passion loss chance</IH_passionLoss>
  <IH_passionLossTip>The chance that a pawn will lose passions during a quickening.</IH_passionLossTip>
  <IH_passionLimit>Passion Limit</IH_passionLimit>
  <IH_passionLimitTip>A hard limit on how many passions a pawn can have, minor passions count as 1 and majors count as 2. -1 to dissable</IH_passionLimitTip>

  <!-- Immortality class stuff-->
  <IH_disabled>disabled</IH_disabled>
  <IH_humanoid>Humanoid</IH_humanoid>
  <IH_animal>Animals</IH_animal>


  <IH_categoriesOn>Show pawn specific settings</IH_categoriesOn>
  <IH_categoriesOff>Hide pawn specific settings</IH_categoriesOff>
  <IH_categoriesTip>Opens the setings section that lets you change/add/remove immortality classes.</IH_categoriesTip>

  <IH_NewClass>New class</IH_NewClass>
  <IH_NewClassTip>Creates a new immortality class which you can edit.</IH_NewClassTip>

  <IH_DeleteClass>Delete Class</IH_DeleteClass>
  <IH_DeleteClassTip>Removes an immorality class, this cannot be undone. To be sure you mean to do this you must slide the slider below all the way to the right</IH_DeleteClassTip>
  <IH_slideConfirm>Slide then click</IH_slideConfirm>
  <IH_slideConfirmTip>To confirm you want to delete this class slide this all the way to the right.</IH_slideConfirmTip>
  <IH_editDefault>Use default ({0})</IH_editDefault>
  

  <IH_ImmortalClassCanBe>Can be immortal</IH_ImmortalClassCanBe>
  <IH_ImmortalClassCanBeTip>Enables/Disables the pawns in this immortality class from being able to spawn as immortal</IH_ImmortalClassCanBeTip>
  <IH_ImmortalClassChance>Immortality Chance: </IH_ImmortalClassChance>
  <IH_ImmortalClassChanceTip>The chance a pawn will spawn with immortality. By default this immortality will be pre-first death but visible chance allows them to be higher tiers of immortals</IH_ImmortalClassChanceTip>
  <IH_ImmortalClassChanceVisible>Visible Chance: </IH_ImmortalClassChanceVisible>
  <IH_ImmortalClassChanceVisibleTip>The chance that a pawn who has generated as immortal will be given a higher tier of immortality between immortality range</IH_ImmortalClassChanceVisibleTip>

  <IH_ImmortalClassPawnsTip>All the pawns in this list are in this immortality class</IH_ImmortalClassPawnsTip>
  <IH_ImmortalClassNonPawnsTip>All the pawns in this list are not in this immorality class. Red means they are not in any immorality class.</IH_ImmortalClassNonPawnsTip>
  <IH_ImmortalClassLoadMissing>Immortals count not find {0} pawn defs, these could be from removed mods. You may clear these old pawns from immortal classes in the immortal options menu, or you may leave them as they are harmless. These are the missing defs: {1}</IH_ImmortalClassLoadMissing>
  
  <!-- Transfer and stunted stuff-->
  <IH_transferSettings>Transfer Settings</IH_transferSettings>
  
  <IH_stealStage1>Immortal</IH_stealStage1>
  <IH_stealStage1Tip>Chance that a pawn will gain hidden immortality from eating the severed head from an immortal</IH_stealStage1Tip>
  <IH_stealStage2>Greater</IH_stealStage2>
  <IH_stealStage2Tip>>Chance that a pawn will gain hidden immortality from eating the severed head from a greater immortal</IH_stealStage2Tip>
  <IH_stealStage3>High</IH_stealStage3>
  <IH_stealStage3Tip>>Chance that a pawn will gain hidden immortality from eating the severed head from a high immortal</IH_stealStage3Tip>
  <IH_stealStage4>Grand</IH_stealStage4>
  <IH_stealStageTip>>Chance that a pawn will gain hidden immortality from eating the severed head from a grand immortal</IH_stealStageTip>
  <IH_stealStage5>Apex</IH_stealStage5>
  <IH_stealStageTip>>Chance that a pawn will gain hidden immortality from eating the severed head from an apex immortal</IH_stealStageTip>


  <IH_stuntedChance>Stunted immortality chance</IH_stuntedChance>
  <IH_stuntedChacneTip>The chance that a pawn who gains immortality will become a stunted immortal</IH_stuntedChacneTip>
  <IH_stuntedBurnChance>Chance a stunted immortal self burns </IH_stuntedBurnChance>
  <IH_stuntedBurnChanceTip>Every rare tick a stunted immortal will roll to see if it self burns. These burns cannot be healed by immortality but will reduce the level of the stunted hediff curing them sooner.</IH_stuntedBurnChanceTip>
  <IH_stuntedBurnRate>The severity of the self burns </IH_stuntedBurnRate>
  <IH_stuntedBurnRateTip>A multiplier that effects the damage of the stunted burns.</IH_stuntedBurnRateTip>
  
  
  
  <!--Default Hediff Stuff-->
  <IH_defaultHediffs>Default Hediffs</IH_defaultHediffs>

  <IH_conditionMax>Max condition progress</IH_conditionMax>
  <IH_conditionMaxTip>The maximum progress conditions should get to, every immortal tick they will be set to this value if it is over this value. Conditions have a lethal severity of 1 and are non-tendable like bloodloss or malnutrition.</IH_conditionMaxTip>
  <IH_diseaseMax>Max disease progress</IH_diseaseMax>
  <IH_diseaseMaxTip>The maximum progress diseases should get to, every immortal tick they will be set to this value if it is over this value. Diseases have a lethal severity of 1 and are tendable like infections of flu.</IH_diseaseMaxTip>
  <!--Hediff Settings Shit-->
  
  <IH_hediffShowOnlyBad>Only bad hediffs</IH_hediffShowOnlyBad>
  <IH_hediffShowOnlyBadTip>Hides all hediffs that have isBad set to false</IH_hediffShowOnlyBadTip>

  <IH_hediffShowOnlyCondition>Only lethal</IH_hediffShowOnlyCondition>
  <IH_hediffShowOnlyConditionTip>Hides all hediffs that do not have a lethal severity</IH_hediffShowOnlyConditionTip>

  <IH_hediffShowOnlyCustom>Only custom</IH_hediffShowOnlyCustom>
  <IH_hediffShowOnlyCustomTip>Hides all hediffs that do not have custom settings.</IH_hediffShowOnlyCustomTip>

  <IH_condition>Condition</IH_condition>
  <IH_conditionTip>A condition hediff has a lethal severity of 1 and is non-tendable such as bloodloss or malnutrition.</IH_conditionTip>
  <IH_disease>Disease</IH_disease>
  <IH_diseaseTip>A disesase hediff has a lethal severity of 1 and is tendable such as the flu or an infection.</IH_diseaseTip>
  <IH_other>Other</IH_other>
  <IH_otherTip>Hediffs that don't fit into the other categories.</IH_otherTip>
  
  <IH_hediffMaxProgress>Max progress: </IH_hediffMaxProgress>
  <IH_hediffMaxProgressTip>The maximum progress this hediff should get to, every tick it will be set to this value if it is over this value.</IH_hediffMaxProgressTip>
  <IH_hediffHealSpeed>Heal speed: </IH_hediffHealSpeed>
  <IH_hediffHealSpeedTip>A multiplier for how fast this hediff heals. If set to 0 it will ignore this hediff</IH_hediffHealSpeedTip>

  <IH_hediffneedToCure>Need to cure: </IH_hediffneedToCure>
  <IH_hediffneedToCureTip>Does a pawn need to cure this hediff before it revives</IH_hediffneedToCureTip>
  <IH_hediffCanGet>Can get </IH_hediffCanGet>
  <IH_hediffCanGetTip>Should a pawn be able to get this hediff? This doesn't full stop a pawn from getting a hediff it just removes it when the immortality healing ticks</IH_hediffCanGetTip>

  <IH_hediffRegrow>regrow: </IH_hediffRegrow>
  <IH_hediffRegrowTip>Hediffs with this enabled will be *saved* to pawns every rare tick and when a hediff is missing that was there before it will be re-added.</IH_hediffRegrowTip>

  <IH_hediffLoadMissing>Immortals could not find {0} hediffs, it is possible they are from unloaded mods. You may clear these old hediff settings in the immortals options page, or leave them as they are harmless. These are the hediffs defs: {1}</IH_hediffLoadMissing>
  
  
  <!-- Other shit-->
  
  
  <IH_Immortals>Immortals</IH_Immortals>
  <IH_Designator_Behead>Behead</IH_Designator_Behead>
  <IH_Designator_BeheadDesc>Cut off the head of a pawn or whatever may pass as a head for the pawn. This will stop any immortals from coming back to life.</IH_Designator_BeheadDesc>
  <IH_MustDesignateBeheadAble>Must designate pawn or creature who is dead or downed with a head.</IH_MustDesignateBeheadAble>
  <IH_Default>   (Default)</IH_Default>
  <IH_DefaultNum>   (Default: {0})</IH_DefaultNum>
  <IH_off>off</IH_off>
  <IH_on>on</IH_on>
  <IH_yes>yes</IH_yes>
  <IH_no>no</IH_no>


  
 
  <IH_CanGetDisease>Can Immortals Get Diseases</IH_CanGetDisease>
  <IH_CanGetDiseaseTip>Will cure immortals of diseases if they contract them, a disease if any tendable fatal hediff.</IH_CanGetDiseaseTip>
  <IH_CanGetConditions>Can Immortals Get Conditions</IH_CanGetConditions>
  <IH_CanGetConditionsTip>Will cure immortals of any conditions, a condition is any non-tendable fatal hediff</IH_CanGetConditionsTip>
  <IH_healScars>Heal Scars</IH_healScars>
  <IH_classPawns>Class pawns</IH_classPawns>
  <IH_nonClassPawns>Other pawns</IH_nonClassPawns>
  
  
  <!--Stops anything with a lethal severity of 1 at the % indicated in the settings so things like malnutrition and what not-->
  <IH_diseaseMaxProg>Stops the progress of a lethal disease at: </IH_diseaseMaxProg>
  <IH_diseaseMaxProgTip>Anything that is tendable with a lethal severity of 100% this includes things like infections and the flu. Set to 100% to disable</IH_diseaseMaxProgTip>
  <IH_conditionMaxProg>Stops the progress of a lethal condition at: </IH_conditionMaxProg>
  <IH_conditionMaxProgTip>Anything that is not tendable with a lethal severity of 100% this includes things like bloodloss and heatstroke</IH_conditionMaxProgTip>

  <IH_firstDeathHeal>Healing speed prior to first resurrection: </IH_firstDeathHeal>
  <IH_firstDeathHealTip>The healing speed of an immortal after they have died their first death and before they have respawned. Changes how long they will be dead on their first death.</IH_firstDeathHealTip>
  
  <!--The names inserted into the chances and transfer rates for the categories-->


  <IH_lesser>Lesser Immortal</IH_lesser>
  <IH_immortal>Immortal</IH_immortal>
  <IH_greater>Greater Immortal</IH_greater>
  <IH_high>High Immortal</IH_high>
  <IH_grand>Grand Immortal</IH_grand>
  <IH_apex>Apex Immortal</IH_apex>

  <!--Enableing and disabling the different types of pawns as well as their chances-->

  <IH_Extractor_Contained_Heads>Contains {0} of {1} severed heads</IH_Extractor_Contained_Heads>
  <IH_Extractor_Awaiting>Awaiting quickening trigger</IH_Extractor_Awaiting>
  <IH_Extractor_Finished>Finished</IH_Extractor_Finished>
  <IH_Extractor_Progress>Progress: {0}, {1}</IH_Extractor_Progress>
  <IH_Extractor_Speed_Bonus>Speed bonus from heat</IH_Extractor_Speed_Bonus>
  
  <!--Allows an exponential difference of immortality based on the size difference-->

  <IH_DaysLeftSeverity>Days remaining </IH_DaysLeftSeverity>


  <IH_partStages>Max base part Hp Settings</IH_partStages>
  <IH_maxPartSize>Max part Hp Limit: </IH_maxPartSize>
  <IH_maxPartSizeTip>Limits the maximum part Hp any immortal can regrow.</IH_maxPartSizeTip>
  <IH_maxPartStage>The maximum base part Hp added to calculate parts they can regrow when an immortal is at the {0} stage</IH_maxPartStage>
  <IH_severityMaxPart>Severity Multiplier : </IH_severityMaxPart>
  <IH_severityMaxPartTip>This value is multiplied by the severity of the immortal hediff. This value is then added to per stage values.</IH_severityMaxPartTip>
  <IH_otherStageSettings>Other max part Hp settings</IH_otherStageSettings>
  <IH_stageValues>Stage Values</IH_stageValues>

  <IH_severityCheck>Check specific immortal severity: </IH_severityCheck>
  <IH_severityCheckTip>Tool to see how specific severities would affect max part Hp</IH_severityCheckTip>
  
  <!--Editing stuff and such-->
  <IH_disable>None</IH_disable>
 
  <IH_hediffsOn>Show heddif specific settings</IH_hediffsOn>
  <IH_hediffsOff>Hide hediff specific settings</IH_hediffsOff>


  <IH_ImmortalClassHealScars>Heal scars: </IH_ImmortalClassHealScars>

  
  <IH_hediffs>Edit hediff specific settings</IH_hediffs>
  <IH_editShowChanged>Show only changed hediffs</IH_editShowChanged>

  <IH_editClearChanged>Clear changed hediffs</IH_editClearChanged>
  <IH_editClearChangedConrfirm>Confirm clear changed hediffs</IH_editClearChangedConrfirm>
  <IH_disease>Disease</IH_disease>
  <IH_condition>Condition</IH_condition>
  
  <IH_editShowGood>Show non-bad hediffs</IH_editShowGood>
  <IH_editShowNonLethal>Show non-lethal hediffs</IH_editShowNonLethal>
  <IH_editRemoveCustom>Remove custom settings</IH_editRemoveCustom>
  <IH_search>Search:</IH_search>

  <IH_editNoMax>No max progress</IH_editNoMax>
  <IH_editNoMaxTip>This condition will progress like normal</IH_editNoMaxTip>
  <IH_editMaxProg>Max progress: {0}</IH_editMaxProg>
  <IH_editDisabled>This condition is disabled for immortals</IH_editDisabled>

  <IH_editCureDead>Have to cure this condition before revive</IH_editCureDead>
  <IH_editCanGet>Can immortals have this condition</IH_editCanGet>
  <IH_editHealHediff>Should this condition heal over time</IH_editHealHediff>

  <IH_stageSteal>{0} head {1} </IH_stageSteal>
  <IH_stageStealChance>immortality chance</IH_stageStealChance>


  <IH_Designator_ExtractorTrigger>Extractor Trigger</IH_Designator_ExtractorTrigger>
  <IH_Designator_ExtractorTriggerDesc>Use this immortal pawn to trigger a mortalis extractor.</IH_Designator_ExtractorTriggerDesc>

  <IH_Designator_Impale>Impale Pawn</IH_Designator_Impale>
  <IH_Designator_ImpaleDesc>Take a piece of steel and drive it through the heart of a pawn. This will stop an immortal from reviving.</IH_Designator_ImpaleDesc>
  <IH_MustDesignateImpaleAble>Must designate downed or dead pawn.</IH_MustDesignateImpaleAble>

  <IH_NoSteel>No steel</IH_NoSteel>

</LanguageData>